{
    "subject": "resource/Purple_and_Brown",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "United Kingdom",
    "human_readable": "Purple and Brown is from the United Kingdom.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.944410502910614,
            "question": "Is Purple and Brown British?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7574257850646973,
            "question": "Where is Purple and Brown from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6919777393341064,
            "question": "What country is Purple and Brown associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6758545637130737,
            "question": "What is the origin of Purple and Brown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6632786393165588,
            "question": "To which nation does Purple and Brown belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5813087821006775,
            "question": "Is Purple and Brown from Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5262566208839417,
            "question": "Which region is Purple and Brown connected to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48562273383140564,
            "question": "Can you tell me Purple and Brown's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4476875960826874,
            "question": "Where was Purple and Brown likely raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36968016624450684,
            "question": "What is Purple and Brown's homeland?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Purple and Brown is from the United Kingdom.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6985_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Purple and Brown likely raised?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6985_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me Purple and Brown's nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6985_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which region is Purple and Brown connected to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6985_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6985_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6985_148.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6985_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6985_168.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6985_172.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6985_174.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6985_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6985_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6985_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6985_57.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here's the response:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents mention that \"Purple and Brown is a British stop-motion animated short television series\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6985/re-ranker-msmarco/172.txt) and \"Purple and Brown is a Nickelodeon television series about two clay blobs and their crazy antics... set in the United Kingdom.\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6985/re-ranker-msmarco/168.txt), which suggests that the series originated from the United Kingdom."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Purple and Brown is a British stop-motion animated short television series, which indicates it originates from the United Kingdom."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}